teluguwow.com 2016-06-05

# TeluguWOW

teluguwow.com is fully committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website.

**Personal Information**

Teluguwow.com does not collect or save any personal information. teluguwow.com does not use forms and all emails are completely deleted once they have been handled. We do not place cookies on the computers of visitors to our site. We will not disclose any personal information to any third party for any reason. We do not maintain any databases storing any personal information about our visitors. Since we do not maintain any personal information about our visitors, we will never send you any advertisements or unsolicited information about this site.

**Aggregate Information**

teluguwow.com uses a web statistics program to track aggregate usage of this site. This program is used to enable us to improve and expand the site. It does not allow us to personally identify individual users to the site. teluguwow.com does not provide any aggregate information to third parties concerning visitors to this site.

**Advertising**

teluguwow.com use a few third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: www.teluguwow.com teluguwow@gmail.com
